FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS, AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
We got a report of a body. Rosebud Hotel.
PREVIOUSLY
It looks like she's been dead for a while.
It's been at least 12 hours.
She was stabbed in three places, but there's not much bleeding.
Do you know the victim?
Her name's Oh Minyeong. She's a concierge.
Men just wouldn't leave her alone.
She's gorgeous.
Have you seen anyone suspicious lately?
Ah! Room 701.
There's a suspect in the seventh-floor suite.
I heard he's a chaebol heir.
He kept calling for Minyeong,
Saying he had requests to make.
- Chunsik? - Isoo!
You've been here three weeks.
- Did you run away from home? - No, I just...
Is it because of Ms. Oh Minyeong?
The person I fell for at first sight is...
It's you, Minyeong.
Minyeong.
I'm sorry. I have a boyfriend.
Minyeong...
Do you know anyone who might've had a grudge against Ms. Oh Minyeong?
I saw everything, you bitch!
You've got it all wrong. It's not me!
You psycho bitch!
Do you have any idea who you're dealing with? Huh?
- Who was she? - It was the hotel owner's wife.
The owner was dating Ms. Oh Minyeong?
There were rumors that he was in love with her.
I have nothing else to say.
I said we're not done.
Let go.
He tried to drag her into Room 709?
That room has been vacant for two months.
I kept that room for my own personal use.
We took the carpet in for testing, and there wasn't enough blood.
I don't think she was murdered here.
She died somewhere else?
What's this?
Are you checking out?
Detective Jin, it's Room 701. I came in to clean,
And I found something that looks like blood.
What?
Kang Chunsik.
:cue
Watch out!
Don't worry. My car's more expensive.
How dare he try to take me on?
Hey, hey.
Vehicle ahead, stop the car.
The trust-fund kid in car 6383!
Stop the car!
What's he doing?
My good citizens!
Chunsik Food's sole heir is on the run!
We are police.
Kang Chunsik is on the run!
Kang Chunsik, stop the damn car!
That brat just won't listen.
Here we go.
- What the hell are you doing? - Mr. Kang Chunsik.
You're under arrest for the murder of Oh Minyeong.
What?
Isoo. Why are you doing this to me?
What do you mean? You just ran from the police.
We're taking you into custody, punk.
Isoo!
EPISODE 6
What kind of steak knife comes with room service?
Why did you run away?
I was just on my way home.
My car's just really fast.
You said Ms. Oh Minyeong left your room around 7:40 p.m.
That's right.
What did you do after that?
Oh, for god's sake.
Answer the question.
I was drinking because I was upset. :cue
And then?
I ran out of alcohol, so I went to the bar.
Evening, sir.
- The usual, please. - Yes, sir.
I was there until around 10:00 p.m.
DETECTIVE PARK JUNYOUNG
The photo below is Rosebud Restaurant's steak knife.
Were you angry Ms. Oh rejected you?
Of course I was.
So you called her back, didn't you?
- You stabbed her with the steak knife. - What?
Minyeong.
Please don't kill me.
What on earth are you talking about?
Here.
- This is Room 701, where you stayed. - That's right.
We found blood there.
And signs that the floor had been cleaned.
Where is the knife?
Wait...
You mean...
Minyeong...
Died in my hotel room?
That's exactly what we're saying.
But I...
I slept there.
Seriously, why is he always passing out?
-  Did you call? -  Yes.
Please lock him up when he's awake.
Is he okay?
He's fine. He'll wake up if you give him some water.
:cue
Hello.
I'm with the police.
Right.
By any chance,
Do you remember this guest?
Ah...
I do.
Did he come here on the night of the 13th?
Yes.
I was supposed to get off at 8:00 p.m.,
But the night staff didn't show, so I was stuck on duty.
I had plans, but I couldn't make it.
What time was that?
It was a little before 8:30 p.m.
Around 8:20.
KEY SUSPECTS KANG CHUNSIK
YEOM JAESEOP, CHA SERAN, YEOM KIJOO
I really don't think it's Chunsik.
Hello?
He came to the bar around 8:20 p.m.
Got it.
Pull up the bar hallway.
Oh, there he is.
It doesn't look like Chunsik's our guy.
He may not look like it, but he's a good kid.
He killed the victim in a fit of rage,
Went up to the bar for a drink,
Returned to get rid of the body,
And wiped the floor.
Kang Chunsik is the only one who can do that.
Then how did he move the body?
Did he carry her?
And even if he knew about Room 709 through the rumors,
How would he get in? He doesn't have a key.
He could've called someone to do it.
Without the camera, we can't confirm anything.
Did you check all the footage?
No, not even half. There's too much to go through.
- Let's split it. Send it over. - Yes, ma'am.
Time of death was around 8:00 to 9:00 p.m.
We have to find everyone who entered the hotel, took the elevator,
Or got off on the seventh floor during that time.
Understood.
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
DETECTIVE DIVISION
Aren't you guys hungry?
Let's order some food.
I'll order it. How about a sandwich?
Sounds good. I'll get a beef sandwich.
Beef.
Detective Joo?
I'll get the Italian B.M.T.
Ooh.
Italian B.M.T.
This is yours, bro.
- This is Detective Joo's. -  Thank you.
Beef sandwich is the way to go.
It's stuffed with meat.
You need ham in a sandwich. :cue
We never see eye to eye.
They're both delicious.
Detective Joo!
- What... - Yes?
You're all...
Can I have a word?
Yes, sir.
What was that?
- Did you arrest the heir of Chunsik Food? - Yes.
Is he definitely guilty?
He's our prime suspect so far.
He also fled, so we arrested him.
What if he's innocent? Huh?
Are you going to make me look bad?
Do the reporters know?
What will you do if he's not the culprit?
Sir.
Why are you so worried?
If it's not him, I'll handle it. I'm friends with his dad. We're mutuals.
In any case, just get it right!
Get it right!
Gosh,
How did someone so timid become a police chief, huh?
SEWON HOSPITAL
KANG JINKYUNG HEMATOLOGIST-ONCOLOGIST
Yes, come in.
Mr. Choi Jeonghun?
Please have a seat.
I've gone over your test results,
And there's a malignant tumor in your stomach.
Uh, right.
Don't worry too much. We can treat it.
Uh, the tumor isn't that large,
But I think surgery will be necessary.
- Uh... - Please don't overthink it.
It's just like a car accident that could happen to anyone.
I'll help you get better.
DETECTIVE JIN ISOO
- Hello? -  Mr. Choi.
Did you go to the hospital?
Yes, I'm there now.
- Did you get checked out? - Yes. They said everything's fine.
That's a relief.
I was scared that you were seriously ill.
What's there to be scared about?
You're the only family I have now.
Don't get sick, okay?
Eat only the good stuff. No whiskey.
All right.
You promised, so it's your turn to see a psychiatrist.
Okay, fine. I'll go after catching the killer.
Gotta go.
All right.
:cue
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
The forensic results are here.
The one who asked Yeom Jaeseop to meet in Room 709 was Ms. Oh Minyeong.
They spoke several times.
Yeom transferred 100 million won to her twice.
Come to Room 709.
These texts sound a little strange.
Where is Yeom Jaeseop right now?
Kyungjin is tracking him.
Yeom Jaeseop left the country!
Where did he go?
Hanoi. He just got on board.
If he disappears, we can't find him.
Contact Hanoi Airport and get immigration...
Oh.
You have a private jet.
How did you know about that?
I saw it on the news.
- Can you catch up with him? -  Of course!
Let's go!
Come on, run!
Captain!
We're off to Hanoi!
We have to catch the killer! Hey!
Run!
Detective Joo! Awesome photo, right?
Am I the only one embarrassed?
Just accept it!
Ta-da!
The Hansu private jet. This is the premium bar.
It has all kinds of drinks
And even a fridge. And a kettle, too.
Oh, this chair. It's really comfortable. Try sitting down.
It's nice.
When do you use this?
Hmm... Whenever.
When I go scuba diving or throw parties.
Ah, I also ride it on December 31st
And follow the setting sun.
Classic rich-people behavior.
It must be nice being rich.
It definitely doesn't hurt.
Hey,
How much does this cost?
This?
- What? - Makes you jealous, right?
I'll lend it to you when you propose.
- Really? - Yes.
I love you, bro.
Mmm. Yeah, me too.
You promised.
- Promise. - Okay, for god's sake.
You all heard, right?
Hey.
Would you lend it to me, too?
You want to get married?
Are you going to propose?
No, I mean,
If the time comes.
You thought that far ahead?
Isn't it a little too soon?
Hey, I'll make a great MC.
We will now begin the wedding
Of Groom Park Junyoung and Bride Yoon Jiwon.
- Please welcome... - Our groom!
Oh?
I'm going to the restroom.
The restroom's up front.
Stupid.
Ladies and gentlemen,
We have arrived at Noi Bai International Airport.
VIETNAM HANOI AIRPORT
Ladies and gentlemen!
This is Jin Isoo Air!
We are urgently looking for Mr. Yeom Jaeseop! :cue
I repeat,
We are urgently looking for Mr. Yeom Jaeseop!
Would Mr. Yeom Jaeseop please have his passport ready
And transfer to this aircraft.
Jin Isoo is here!
Mr. Yeom Jaeseop!
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
You met Ms. Oh Minyeong at 7:50 p.m. on the day of the murder.
Just come clean. We've already checked everything.
Why did you meet her?
Because of my wife. I needed to talk to her.
What did you talk about?
She was angry after your wife grabbed her by the hair, right?
Yes.
So I tried to make it up to her.
I'm sorry.
Whatever.
When the new hotel opens up, I'll make you a manager there.
- Really? - Of course.
Oh, you.
Jaeseop!
Are you in there?
I'll go first, so you can come out later.
I didn't see her after that.
What time was that?
I think it was around 8:00 p.m.
What did you do before going back to your office at 8:20 p.m.?
I was on the phone, at the stairwell.
At the stairwell? With whom?
It was a business call.
OH MINYEONG BANK STATEMENT
You gave Ms. Oh 200 million won.
100 million two months ago, and another 100 million last week.
It was a form of compensation.
Because my wife hit her.
Oh, he must be really well-off.
Two hundred million won.
Are you going to keep lying?
She blackmailed you, didn't she?
When are you going to send me the money?
If you keep this up, you're going to regret it.
"Do not test my patience."
What's the reason?
Why did she blackmail you?
That has nothing to do with this case.
That's for us to decide.
You'd had enough of the blackmail, so you killed her.
That's not true.
She was definitely alive when I left the room.
If she were killed in that room,
It means someone was trying to frame me.
Open your eyes.
Open your eyes wide.
Mmm.  Okay.
"Leo"?
Who's Leo?
Leonardo DiCa... Him?
ROSEBUD HOTEL STAFF ROSTER
FRONT DESK JEON YUJIN
EMPLOYEE RECORD
It's him. Jeon Yujin.
NAME JEON YUJIN
Right, Mr. Jeon Yujin.
He was the one in the CEO's office.
- Check the camera outside the office. -  Okay.
That's a bit strange.
What employee barges into the CEO's office?
We have a new suspect.
The CEO's mistress.
No, his male lover.
:cue
Mr. Yeom.
The one you love is Jeon Yujin, isn't it?
I didn't know I'd turn out this way.
I'm married, and I even have a kid.
I fell for him like crazy.
TWO MONTHS EARLIER
- Sir. - Yes, Mr. Yu.
- These are our new employees. - Ah.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome to our hotel.
-  Cheers. -  Cheers.
- Let me pour you one. - Thank you.
I look forward to working with you.
Enjoy your food.
Sir, let me pour you a glass, too.
Thank you.
Thank you for dinner.
Have a safe trip home.
Take care.
Sir...
Watch your step.
Thank you.
Stop the car.
Get in. I'll take you home.
Dry yourself.
Don't start anything if you're not sure.
I don't want to get hurt anymore.
Yujin.
Even if you're an alien,
Or a man...
I really don't know anymore.
Let's see this through to the end.
We met secretly in Room 709.
Mmm. It's good.
Yes, it's delicious.
Do you like wine?
Oh, I do. :cue
It felt like a dream.
But...
It didn't last long.
Then the blackmail started.
Mr. Yeom.
Why are you so cheap?
You really think this is enough?
So I sent her 100 million won.
Then my wife caused a scene, so I sent her another 100 million.
But that day, she said she wanted to see me.
Minyeong, what do you want me to do?
My feet are killing me.
I think I might quit.
I don't want to come into work,
And I'm sick of all the annoying guests.
Mr. Yeom.
I'd like a leaving bonus.
I don't have any money.
If you don't have money, what does that make me?
Honey! Get out here!
Are you in there?
Where are you?
Look who's busted.
Come out here!
Shall I open the door?
Wait.
Okay, fine.
I want one billion won.
I need time.
Will a month do?
Mr. Yeom, I'm going to take leave starting tomorrow.
Yujin.
Let's end this.
What's wrong? Did Oh Minyeong blackmail you again?
There's nothing more to say. Let's end it.
I told you not to start if you're unsure.
You said you'd see it through.
This is the end! Don't you get it?
Then what am I supposed to do?
How can I work here when I have to see you?
Then you leave! You can just quit!
Jaeseop.
Then why did you flee?
When I heard Oh Minyeong had died,
I had a bad feeling.
Had Yujin killed her?
No, it couldn't be.
But when I heard she died in Room 709,
I thought Yujin had killed her in that room
To get revenge on me.
I didn't know what to do,
So I just ran away.
Is this something you can just run away from?
By the way,
Why is it "Leo"?
It's Yujin's zodiac sign.
Ah.
His zodiac sign.
Right, you're quite the romantic.
Ah.
His zodiac sign. :cue
How did it go?
It was a tragic love story.
It touched my heart. Ah.
Let's look into Jeon Yujin.
Kyungjin, trace his movements on that day.
- And find out where he is now. - Got it.
Take out all your belongings.
Mr. Yeom.
Did you...
Kill Minyeong?
It was you, asshole. You killed her, didn't you?
Come here.
Come here right now!
Do you have any idea how much I loved her?
Kang Chunsik! Get back.
What are you going to do about Minyeong?
What are you going to do about me?
Jeon Yujin answered the call at 8:05 p.m.
Hello?
Yujin.
Let's end this.
He left the CEO's office and went to the bar.
He must've seen Chunsik there.
He would've thought of using Room 701.
Because it was well-known that Kang Chunsik liked Ms. Oh.
I found the last footage of Ms. Oh.
I think she was on the roof.
She got on the staff elevator at 8:40 p.m.
She must have hidden out on the roof to avoid Mr. Yeom's wife.
Fifteen minutes.
Where was Jeon Yujin during this time?
Back to the changing room.
He must've gone to get his radio and the master key.
This was when he decided to kill her.
He snuck into Room 701.
Ms. Oh.
A call came in from Room 701.
He told her Chunsik had called for her.
All we have is the motive.
No murder weapon,
And the radio call wouldn't have been logged.
Where's Jeon Yujin after that?
:cue
The elevator.
There's only an eight-minute gap.
In that time, he killed the victim,
Moved the body, and cleaned up?
That's impossible, isn't it?
- It's impossible, without an accomplice. - No, wait.
Why move the body?
He saw Chunsik at the bar
And called her to Room 701 to dump it on Chunsik.
That's true.
There's no reason to move the body.
What if after killing her,
He wanted to get revenge on Yeom Jaeseop and moved the body?
No, that can't be done in eight minutes.
This wasn't a premeditated murder.
How can there be an accomplice?
What on earth could have happened?
Who moved the body and even cleaned up?
Someone who knows that the security camera was broken.
Someone who can move without drawing attention
And move the body without raising any suspicion.
Someone who has access to all the rooms.
Someone who can clean perfectly.
- Housekeeping. -  No way.
What about housekeeping?
Yeom could've given the order after finding out Jeon had killed her.
I killed her.
I...
I ended up killing her.
I'll take care of it.
Get out of there right now.
In the room he personally used?
He probably hid the body first to deal with later.
We'll go to the hotel, so identify the housekeeping staff.
And find out where Jeon dumped his jacket.
-  Understood. - Okay.
How could it be one of those ladies?
- It's so good. - It's really delicious.
Now I see why it's 100,000 won.
Is there anyone you can rule out?
There is.
Gosh, you keep calling us ladies and flattering us like that.
If that was an act, she deserves an Oscar.
There you are.
What? What is it?
Did you find the killer?
Uh, well...
- We have something to ask you. - What is it?
Were any of the housekeeping staff
Acting suspiciously on the day of the murder or the next day?
What? Us, the housekeeping staff?
What are you talking about?
Someone moved Ms. Oh Minyeong's body.
Someone from the housekeeping staff?
Who?
It's a possibility.
Did anyone seem odd?
Oh...
What is it?
:cue
She was cleaning the cart.
She said she spilled coffee on it.
My gosh.
What are you doing?
I spilled some coffee.
- Really? - Yes.
You startled me.
You should clock out. I'll tidy up in here.
- Okay. - Bye.
We found her. It's Na Yeonhong.
EMPLOYEE RECORD NA YEONHONG
JEON YUJIN
She's Jeon Yujin's mom.
She knew her son killed someone and covered it up.
MINYEONG
We'll find evidence if we check the cart.
Let's arrest Ms. Na Yeonhong first.
Wait.
Let me talk to her first.
:cue
Something on your mind?
No, nothing.
Would you like some tea?
Thank you.
Here.
One moment, please.
You must be tired.
I'm fine. Everyone has to make a living.
My mom
Died when I was young.
Gosh, I'm sorry to hear that.
I was lonely, so I acted out
And did a lot of stupid things.
No matter how badly I messed up,
She'd be on my side, right?
Of course.
To a mother, her child will always be her baby.
There's nothing she wouldn't do for her child.
You're right.
My mom would've been the same.
But if I...
Committed an unforgivable crime,
And if my mom was punished for trying to protect me,
I would probably...
Never be able to forgive myself.
Please tell me
What happened.
I killed her.
This isn't the right thing for Yujin.
Please reconsider.
I'm sorry.
Please tell the truth.
Everything will come to light in the end.
I killed Ms. Oh Minyeong.
Get up.
Ms. Na Yeonhong,
You're under arrest for Ms. Oh Minyeong's murder.
You have the right to an attorney
And the right to remain silent.
You won't be penalized for remaining silent.
Stop right there!
Wait! :cue
No, Yujin!
- I killed her. -  Yujin!
No.
Yujin...
My mom did nothing wrong.
No, Yujin, no.
Yujin, my baby.
Yujin, no.
Yujin!
No, not you.
- No, Yujin. - I'm sorry.
My baby.
I was the one who killed her.
Me!
Oh, my goodness.
Please, no, my baby.
My baby.
You're right.
I called her over to Room 701 and killed her.
What are you doing?
Just stop.
Stop what?
You got your money.
So stop blackmailing us.
I basically struck gold here.
Would you stop if you were me?
You...
Are you out of your mind?
Yes, I'm out of my mind.
Then I heard the body was found in Room 709,
So I thought Mr. Yeom had covered up for me.
I had no idea it was my mom.
I guess you didn't tell the hotel
You were working with your mother.
No.
She's been working there for a while,
And I...
I started working this year.
My mom said we should act like strangers,
Because nothing good would come from it.
After she got divorced, I was all she had.
Because of me...
My mom...
All you're worried about is your mom after you murdered someone?
You're a murderer.
You ended someone's life.
Was it worth all that?
:cue
Mr. Yeom Jaeseop, Mr. Kang Chunsik, you're cleared of all suspicion.
You are free to go.
- Jaeseop! - Dad!
What happened, huh?
Did you kill her?
No.
Then what?
You're cheating, aren't you?
It's all over. Just stop.
You're a coward until the end.
Why did you even start it?
It's Leo.
Seran.
Yujin is the one I love.
Yujin?
Wait,
Who the hell is Yujin?
Oh, my god.
Then why did Minyeong die?
She was a blackmailer.
She blackmailed them and was murdered.
My sweet, angelic Minyeong
Was a blackmailer?
Don't pass out, seriously.
Huh?
Kang Chunsik!
Now even a man is...
A man...
Come on, seriously?
Is passing out contagious now? What the heck?
For god's sake!
Hello, 119? Yes, this is Gangha Police Station.
Let's go drink some soju, team.
Yes, sir.
- We should go for a beer, too. - Sounds great.
I have plans, so I'll get going.
Stay for one drink. We caught the killer.
I'm already late. I'm off.
- Okay, bye. - See you tomorrow.
Have a good evening!
What kind of team leader skips drinks with the team?
Come on, bro. Let's go.
My feelings are hurt.
- Seriously, I'm hurt. -  Let's go.
She got a boyfriend? What's with her?
-  Cheers! -  Cheers!
Mmm!
Hey, this flavor is insane.
I've been craving this lately.
They're famous for their gopdoritang, but this is good too, right?
It's so sweet and savory.
I can't stop eating it.
I'll have to come back next time.
With who? Your girlfriend?
No.
By myself.
I saw they have meals for one here.
I'm coming back for lunch by myself.
Mmm...
:cue
This case was driven by an all-consuming love.
Love is all-consuming by nature.
Is it?
Is it, Junyoung?
I've never had an office romance before.
It's fun to secretly date a coworker, right?
How does it feel? Tell me, I'm curious.
That's enough.
I don't know who it is.
I just had a feeling you were dating a coworker.
Yeah, who could it be? I'm dying to know.
Ah!
No wonder he always volunteered to go to the morgue.
I noticed a long time ago.
I've been dating since I was in seventh grade.
I'm a dating expert.
Will you two just shut up?
I don't think so. I'm going to say more.
You should be keeping things professional.
The autopsy room? How dare you!
The autopsy room, what?
- It's where your love blossomed. - The autopsy room!
You guys are awful.
Jiwon.
Yes, we're dating.
Is that really something to tease him about?
- What's with you two? - No.
We should celebrate. Right, Kyungjin?
Yes, of course.
Right.
Here, let me pour you one.
I thought you were the Grim Reaper.
Leave my Junyoung alone.
You know what my job is, right?
- Congratulations. - Congratulations from me, too!
- Cheers. - Cheers.
That hits the spot.
How did you two end up together?
Well, we just
Met by chance and ended up eating together.
That wasn't by chance.
What?
I timed it and waited for you.
Waited!
Uh...
Really? I had no idea.
Dummy.
Even a guy that clueless has a girlfriend.
I know.
I don't get it at all. Cheers.
Remember, I asked you where you lived.
Uh, you look well.
That's freelancing for you.
It's great not being a cop.
All those reports. Just thinking about it ruins my drink.
What about you?
What's it like being back at Gangha?
I like it.
There's a real thrill in catching murderers one by one.
I kind of miss that.
What's Jin Isoo like?
Jin Isoo is
Resourceful and quick on his feet.
It's fun working with him.
Ah...
I thought you'd be missing me.
Uh, you're the one who decided to leave.
Here.
Cheers.
He's coming back in two days.
I've got everything ready.
:cue
Sometimes, I suddenly can't breathe.
For no reason at all,
I feel like the walls are closing in when I'm inside places like elevators.
I want to hear your story first.
What kind of story?
Let's start with your parents.
Your brother, the one you trusted the most, killed your parents.
I'd like to hear how you feel about that.
Did you know that I caught a psychiatrist?
She hypnotized me and even killed people.
That's why I'm not a big fan of psychiatrists.
I'd rather you just give me the medication,
Instead of wasting time.
You experienced some traumatic events in the past
And also became the target of bombings recently.
This is likely why you are experiencing these symptoms.
Talking honestly about your feelings
And finding closure can really help your recovery.
You think talking about it
Is enough to give me closure?
Let's give it a try.
I'll have to find another hospital.
I'll give you the medication.
Whenever you feel like talking, we can talk then.
ECSTASY A BREATHLESS FALL
CLIMAX LIGHT SCATTERED ACROSS THE UNIVERSE
DISSOLUTION THE SILENCE OF WHISPERING REEDS
YU SEONGWON, THE SCULPTOR WHO CAPTIVATED THE EUROPEAN ART WORLD,
RETURNS AFTER 4 YEARS TO HOLD A SOLO EXHIBITION IN KOREA
RETURN YU SEONGWON'S SOLO EXHIBITION
:cue
DISSOLUTION THE SILENCE OF WHISPERING REEDS
FLEX X COP 2 EPISODE 6
AS THE MYSTERY DEEPENS, YU SEONGWON EMERGES
Special Cast. Choi Dukmoon, Lee Suk
♪ Every move was never mine ♪
♪ I don't take the checkmate ♪
Park Jaeha's magic show! These tickets are impossible to get.
He died in a fire mid-show.
The escape routine went as planned.
Something did feel off, though.
- A premonition? - Yes.
This was murder, not an accident.
Someone poured kerosene inside the coffin.
Who made the coffin?
Mr. Park Jaeha?
- I'm Park Jaehyung. -  Twins?
Who could do something so horrific?
Please don't touch.
It was three days earlier.
How are a gangster and a magician linked?
Bring that bastard in.
Let go. Did you kill him?
If I did, you wouldn't even find a body.
He knew he was going to die?
Betting against me takes that much.
Joo Hyera.
Got a lot on your mind?
Still chasing Yu Seongwon?
YU SEONGWON RETURNS AFTER 4 YEARS TO HOLD A SOLO EXHIBITION IN KOREA
That's why you came back, isn't it?
I get how you feel.
It's a case you can never forget.
But we already verified Yu Seongwon's alibi.
You're obsessed.
Huh?
That's what ruins a detective.
It's not an obsession.
Yu Seongwon...
Will kill again.
And I'm going to stop him.
Translated by Hyesoo Lee